[{"answer": "Yeah, we are actually -- we're flying in to Tacloban about two hours ago.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "And what are you hearing about the scale of devastation down there and indeed, the other islands you touched on which they may not even have got to, yet?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "At this point no.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Do they have any idea yet on the 6th times that this hit the islands, how many of those islands have been affected?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "It has to be through the international aid agencies.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What is the best way to help right now?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "What was your thought as you were taking it?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Absolutely correct, Piers.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What is the impression that you're getting on the ground?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Really, just small technicalities.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "I mean in terms of the terminology used here, is there much substantial difference between a massive storm surge like this and a tsunami?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well we were already getting ready for the massive storm because we knew it was a very strong super typhoon.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "When did you realize this was a really massive storm?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Oh, the wind was -- I can describe this to on like -- it was very scary.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "And what was the feeling?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, actually, the desperate need of course is food, water, shelter right now because all the homes are destroyed.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What do you think is the most desperate need right now?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, this wasn't the biggest.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Is it really getting worse or is this a predictable weather pattern that recurs from generation to generation?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Well, my view is that of a journalist to introduce a lot of scientist.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, even though I'm a skeptic, I don't know of anyone that denies climate change.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Isn't under compensating, under reacting denying climate change in the end more dangerous?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "You should not do that, sir -- to say that we don't know.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "PENCER: Which part is not true, Mark?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "It's a dismal number Piers, the Administration, you know, won't confirm this numbers but they're not disputing them and they are supposed to put out their own numbers later this week and it sounds like they're just going to take that better pill once this week officially on the record if you will when they do that.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "So John the rumor is as going to the Wall Street Journal that just 50,000 people in America had so far enrolled into ObamaCare, if that is true, that is pretty appalling isn't it?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Look, there's no question the President is going to stay with her through this storm.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "If these figures carry on that level, would you be buying any stock in Kathleen Sebelius?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Gosh, there are so many different things.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "From what you went through, what is the hardest thing to deal with and how do you deal with it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Incredibly, you've carried on being a great mom, working ridiculously hard as I'm sure Amy will too.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What's my game plan to survive this?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I think that, you know, I called cancer a bit of a blessing, because it puts your life in perspective.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "You know, continuing, trying to live a normal life, how easy is that to do?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "You know, I would imagine it's different for different women.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What's the reality like?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I feel great, my prognosis is excellent and I chanted a bit when they said, \"Will you come and join Piers tonight?\"", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Final question, how are you feeling?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "You know, prevention does not yet exist.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "How important is early to detection and immediate action?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "But do you think it's essential in cases like that?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, it was Angelina Jolie who gave me the courage.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "It's obviously not a club Zoraida that anybody wants to be a member of, but how important is it for public figures do you think to be as courageous as you have been and others in that position like Angelina?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "You know, I think she said it best in her op-ed, \"She feels no less of a women.\"", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "How is she doing and how is she coping having announced to all this to the world with the reality of what her life now is?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "1:30, really soon here.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "So, what time do you getting up tomorrow?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Can you give us any indication at the moment of the scale of this disaster?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "And obviously there are a number of typhoons every season in the Philippines, is this the worst that you can ever remember?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Oh yes, we have 22 countries that have already pledged financial assistance, medical assistance, rescue and relief volunteers, temporary shelters like tents and so on.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "And are you getting the international help that you need and is it coming fast enough?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, we're urging them to contact the Google website that has been set up for missing persons, the embassy and the consulate also is providing numbers that they can contact in case they want to get information from us.", "docId": "131111pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What is the best way that they can get that information?", "qSentId": 478}]